(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-27T05:47:05.456199",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
Hey, deadbeats! What's up?!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to me!
Hey guys, what's up?
Thank you very much for coming to my very first ever 3D live concert!
I see all you deadbeats and chat going wild right now. What is up?
And just like that, Calliope's dead. Bye-bye!
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. It's a joke. It's a joke.
Now we're here to celebrate. Why are we starting off in this room? I don't know.
Maybe because I'm nervous as hell and I want to talk to my friends.
友達と一緒に話したいよ。緊張してるからね。
I want to talk with my friends. I'm so nervous.
Because I'm nervous. I'm so I'm so nervous.
So I thought, why not do a little fun game with my friends who have been with me since the beginning and afterward new friends too that I've made along the way.
Why don't we play a game or something so I can calm down before this big concert? What do you guys think?
Is that okay? Is that okay, deadbeats?
Happy birthday, Daddy. Calm down! No. No. I refuse.
You watch yourself. Mister, you watch yourself. I'm looking at you.
Don't you tell me to calm down. I'm too excited.
Dad needs to work out. I do need to go back to the gym.
But you know what? After today, after today, I'm gonna be extra strong muki muki.
Yeah, especially after today's game. Today's game is going to require some 3D movement. I thought, hey, why not? We're 3D today. So let's do some things in 3D.
Let's do some actions and maybe, I don't know, have my friends try to guess what I'm doing. Maybe that will be cool. So, anyway, that's what I thought.
So, yeah, yeah, yeah, let's enjoy a game of charades, charades with my friends in HoloEN.
And I have some friends from ID joining, and also a friend from JP will be here as well. So, let's get the party started. Let's start! 始まりますー！
And I have some friends from ID joining, and also a friend from JP will be here as well. So, let's get the party started. Let's start! Here we go!
Play's game!
Let's do it.
We've got two different groups of people,
just so you guys know, we had to split them up.
Too many cool friends, so...
Let's see if we can get 'em in here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, here we go. Here we go, here we go.
Ooh, who's it gonna be? Who's it gonna be?
Who's gonna be joining us?
By the way, feel free to use the hashtag, if you want, it's right here.
I want to see your screenshots. Please show me your screenshots.
Okay, everyone come in from the first group, please come here.
Wah!
Hello!
I heard a wah!
Wah!
I hear many friends.
So many friends!
You are so talented!
No, stop, I'm embarrassed!
I'm embarrassed! How could this be?
I'm embarrassed! I'm so embarrassed!
I have my friends here today. We've got Sana, IRyS, Baelz, Ina, and Lui-chan in group number one. Hello guys!
Hello! Can I get your jikoshoukai first so everybody... Thank you, I'm so happy.
Please first, jikoshoukai.
No, stop! Stop! Stop it! Stop it! Ya net!
Man, no, you don't get to look down... So cute, I'm gonna die!
Okay, okay, you're cute. Ungh. No, she can't... She can't...
Baka baka baka baka. Oh, thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Yankee dakara! Thank you Ponpoko. Thank you.
That wasn't part of the game. That wasn't part of the game.
Before we start the game though, can you introduce yourselves please, from Sana? Sana.
Ah yes, it's Sana Tsukumo from Hololive English Council! I am a mere...
Not your space, dude! What are you talking about?
Thank you Sana, you're so sweet.
How about IRyS?
Uh IRyS, it's IRyS Hololive EN Project HOPE, VSinger/VTuber.
And I am so excited for Calli's 3D debut and also from Calli's number one fan in Japan.
Hey, hold on a minute. Thank you. I see, I see.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, that makes sense.
If I could really properly make a heart I would right now, but it's a little difficult. Anyway, close enough, close enough. You get the message.
Thank you IRyS. How about... How about my little sister?
Little sis? What's up? It's me, Mumei! Hey guys, hi, I have infiltrated.
I am... This is my big sister, guys. It's her birthday, and I wanted to come say hi and...
Oh, oh yeah, I'm from Holocath. I'm not leaving without a signature.
Okay. You'll get one. Oh, you're still bringing up the boob!
Oh my gosh. You'll get one, you silly freaking rat!
I want like a signature on my leg. On my leg, please.
Is that what you want? You want a signature?
Yes!
Oh, thank you. It's up to you where I sign, so...
Never washing that part of my body ever again. Nope, never.
How about... how about our favorite taco? Ina, you want to introduce yourself?
Wah! Good morning, afternoon, evening. It's Ninomae Ina'nis from Hololive English Myth, the proudest... proudest gentleman of Calli...
So proud that Calli had a birthday. Wah!
I love you, Ina. Thank you for coming today. I'm so happy.
Man, you know I love you, dude. Gosh dang it, when are we going to get on the same stage, right?
I want a boko boko fate in the face. Boko boko.
And then who do we have last? We have my favorite kohai.
Ah! Oh, she's doing that.
Yeah. Mattakane. Hi, I am Takane Lui from the secret society Holox.
Yeah. You are so cute everyday, but you were so cute more than usual.
Ah, Lui-chan daisuki! Daisuki!
Happy birthday! Thank you so much, Lui-chan. Lui-chan mo kawaii! Kite kurete arigatou. Thank you for coming.
Ja, shall we start the game? Yeah! Let's do it. Come and more!
Okay, let's go!
First word.
Okay, what's the move?
Okay, the audience—the audience can see and I can see, but the girls can't see the word, okay?
So they're going to guess—guess me, okay? Right.
All right, here's number one. Let me see.
Oh, no. How am I supposed—okay, hold on. Hold on.
Karate? Karate?
Um, martial arts?
Martial arts? Fighting?
Ninja? Ninja? Ninja?
Yeah, you got it! I'm a ninja! Ninja run!
Once I pulled out the Naruto run, you guys knew—you guys knew I'm a ninja.
Yeah. I feel good about that one. Ninja! Ninja! That's ninja.
And don't bring—don't bring Yuroa Chang in my chat, any of you. J-Chad will ban you. She will ban you. We don't do that here.
She's a samurai. Yes.
Yuroa Chang is a samurai, not a ninja. Not ninja, okay?
Please remember, okay?
Now, next word, let's go.
Oh, no. Okay, this is going to be kind of hard.
Okay. Um, oh. Oh. Dang it.
Okay. Cartwheel?
Um. This is going to be super—
Um. Um. Levitation?
Um. Opera singer?
Hold on, I'm trying to find a way to—super singer?
Okay, I hope I don't get in trouble for this. They're going to beat the shit out of me if I get in trouble for this.
Okay. Uh, I'm trying to—Titanic!
Here. Uh, uh. Uh. Uh. Titanic?
Titanic?
I—at least descending?
That's right! That's right! So you got it!
It's—it's IRyS! It's supposed to be IRyS!
See, I'm singing and I'm descending. Descending!
I tried to get on like a swivel chair, but the chair started moving around. I was like, "Shit, I'm getting in trouble."
Oh, my gosh.
You got it right. I don't know if descending was that much of a—with that big of a magnitude. I mean, yeah, you did—you did descend three times, IRyS.
Three times.
I had to climb up on something to descend. I mean, that was hard.
Yeah, I guess that's true. That's what I figured out about midway, when I was like, "This isn't going to work."
But, yeah, nice job.
All right, the last question mark—last question, last question, maybe it's question. Last question.
It's supposed to be hard, so let's go. Here we go.
Oh, no. Helm—okay, hold on.
These round circle—swimming or eating?
Eating! Eating ramen! Person out of eating contest.
Oh, eating contest? Speed eating?
Um, Uzukai? No, Mikai? Uzukai?
Chicken? Uzukai! Mikai!
Uzukai? Eating? Eating contest?
Slurping soup? Slurping? Ramen?
Yeah, yes, but, uh, person eating giant ramen.
That's right! Yeah! Someone eating a large bowl of ramen!
Nice job. I was worried about that one.
I didn't know if you'd get the first part, but I think I illustrated the large bowl with my impeccable 3D tracking.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, uh, nice job. Wow, you guys are smart.
Dang, I think—I think that's all. Wow.
You guys blazed through it.
Your movements were easy to understand.
Oh, my gosh, that's crazy. You guys are nuts.
Dang, we should do this more often when everybody gets a chance to be in 3D someday.
Charades party with everyone, yeah?
How show us? How show us?
Man, you guys, please—please someday, think about how crazy that would be if—if that was what we did just now and it was so hilarious. Imagine all of us together.
Yakusoku. Full of ramen. Yakusoku desu.
Yakusoku desu. Promise me? Promise.
Okay. I'll drink a thousand needles.
Oh, wow. Oh, that—please don't hurt yourself.
Please don't. Please don't.
Anyway, I'll see you guys later. Thank you so much for coming!
Thank you! I love you! Bye-bye!
Oh, man, it's so nice to have my friends.
But guess what? They're not the only guests that came today. No, no.
We have several more guests that will be joining us in the next group.
Why don't you ladies come on in?
Come here, come here!
Oh my gosh! Please!
Woah, jump more? Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Save your energy, Ollie.
I knew you just want to see them bounce.
Kiara is giving me the good idol advice, she knows what I need to be doing right now.
Sorry, let me calm down.
Yeah, save your energy, you have a whole performance probably ahead of you, right? Yes, you are right.
Dang it!
There you go. Okay. Calm pose, there we go.
Big breath, big breath. Breathe in, oh big breath, big breath, breathe out!
Okay, breathe in, breathe out.
Okay, we're fine, we're fine now.
Okay, who do we have here today? Oh my gosh, some of my favorite, some of my favorite ladies in the whole world.
Oh my goodness, thank you so much for coming today. We have both ID and of course EN
Myth being represented here, please introduce yourselves, first starting from Reiny, my fishing buddy!
Yay! Attention please, Pavolia Reine, from whole-life ID Generation 2, also Calli's fishing buddy, also a big fan.
Everybody's a fan!
Everybody's suddenly- well, I mean you guys have always been supporting me, so thanks, I appreciate it.
Thank you my- my sweet fishing buddy, love you so much Reine.
Nay!
And how about um, how about how about my Apex buddy for the the two times I've ever played Apex.
We've got crazy Ollie, did I do it right?
You did it so well.
Hi! Zombawa, super kawaii zombie idol. Crazy Ollie desu. Calli-oupisan-senpai!
A wife slash daughter slash mother-in-law relationship is a little bit-
a foggy here, but glad to be here!
Eh?
Hold on, I didn't get the memo for- Wait, did you say wife?
Wife?
Did you propose to me?
Yeah, but you tricked me.
All you guys are tricked by Ollie, Ollie, Ollie, Ollie, you watch yourself.
Next up, we've got HoloEN's number one detective Amelia Watson. Hello, introduce yourself.
Watson! Hi Calli! Hello everybody, I'm Hololive's detective,
Watson Amelia! What's up? Konichiwa Watson, I'm so happy to be here Calli.
I'm so proud of you, you look so beautiful.
Thank you!
Watson, thank you so much, I appreciate that.
Oh man, I'm so glad I get to do 3D stuff. You're also doing really awesome 3D stuff too, so I hope we get to do some fun stuff in the future, yatta!
I can't wait!
Let's do it!
And we can't forget about my idol mentor, apparently Kijima- wait, no, Takane Shiara.
And I am, apparently, a pro for Charades because I got the- the testing prompts
in- within one second.
Oh my gosh, that is true, that is true, and in the beginning there, you immediately knew.
But that was something else, something that you like know well. You knew that I was pretending to be an idol.
No no no, that was- that's not because of that, I'm just really good at Charades, I'll prove it to you Calli.
What is also- it's also because you are just really, really good at
showing those moves and expressing yourself, right?
I have too much fun!
I have too much fun in 3D, it's like all of a sudden I see myself like on the screen
and I'm like "Oh man, I want to jum-", I won't jump.
I won't jump.
I'm going to stay calm.
Hey, please jump! Please jump!
Ollie, please don't tell YourSenpai what to do.
Ollie, I can't do that, I do got to save my energy.
Well, shall we begin the game then? Let's go!
Let's go!
All right, first word.
Here we go.
First word, oh no!
I'm so- okay, here we go.
Oh, hair washing, washing hair.
Baking.
Horse riding? You're frying! You're here!
What? Making your cooking?
Playing the piano? No, a xylophone? No, a drum? What?
It's like you're- you're tying your hair and then you're- you're eating, cooking, cooking.
Close, making pizza, making ramen.
You're tying your hair so like the hair doesn't get-
A job of a chef, a food worker.
Making dough, making bread.
Making a knish? Okay, watch this. Yes, that's it! You got it Watson, you got it!
Sushi Master! I'm the Sushi Master!
So I guess my- I guess my sushi rolling technique- Wait, did they tuck your hand behind your head?
Because I was-
Sushi chefs like maybe have like a little cooking hat or bandana or something?
I don't know, maybe I'm an idiot. Well, why do you hammer the sushi?
Is that how you make it? I don't know. Don't you chop the sushi like this? And you're making like... I don't know.
Well, at least... at least I'm in... maybe that's just a very American perspective, but at least... at least Watson got it, maybe that's why.
Anyway, cut them right across. Yeah. Oh, thank goodness, thank goodness. I thought that I was going to lose that one. Number two! Question number two, let's go.
All right. Oh boy. Oh, this one's too easy. I can do this one. Okay.
Watch closely. Oh. Uh-huh.
Kiara! I know! Takanashi Kiara!
Yes! I'm Takanashi Kiara! Too easy! All I have to do is pull out the kick and be like, "It's the kick, your kick!" You do it with a lot more finesse than I do, but...
That's nice.
I like... I like the angle that you kick, that's good. Oh, thank you. Should I try it again? Thank you. Kiara can do it without moving her body as much as me.
Yeah. I feel like you're giving us a lot today. Well, I don't really know what you mean by that, but anyway, question number three! Question number three, the last, most difficult question. Here we go.
[ホラー映画で最初に死ぬ人]
[The First Person to Die in a Horror Movie]
Okay. No. Oh, no. This isn't possible. Okay, all right, hold on. Okay. Hold on. Think, Calli, think. What...
Kiara! What are you doing? Sushi?
Oh, no! Granny's prank!
Prank, I think. Bad guy killing someone?
Close, you're very close.
A murderer killing someone?
Yes, villain, stabbing someone, a criminal and somebody died.
Oh, no, begging for mercy and dying, dying.
Well, maybe if I can use my fingers. Your fingers. Okay, okay. Okay.
A tiny bulb. What number is this? Two! Two! No. One! Yes, it's one.
One. One. One guy stabbing someone. One punch! One. Number one! One guy running away!
One guy being killed. Close. What's specifically more about them?
One dead guy. One... I'm going to kill whoever chose this question. I'm going to kill them.
I think I might lose this one, guys.
Reverberator... murderer...
Dyings. My friend... the murderer is going to kill my friend. Please don't kill me. No. My friends are alive and I am dead.
Someone died. Someone died. People died while being killed.
I lost this one.
Died by being stabbed to death? Bleeding to death?
That was too freaking specific. Okay, the answer was "the first person to die in a horror movie".
How am I supposed to indicate that I'm the first person? That's difficult! That's hard, but you guys got it for the most part. Why can you be so specific? Right, I know, but you guys got it for the most part. You guys did your best. We all did our best, yeah.
Ah, but you know what, that was fun with you guys, honestly. Oh, man, I'm so glad we got to play a little game together. You guys need to get over here too and do some 3D with me, okay?
Yeah. Of course, I'm waiting for you.
I will! I hope you'll keep watching, because...
Thanks for coming and making time for me. I know it's really early for some folks here and really inconvenient timing, so thank you so much for being here to support me and if you check out the concert...
Don't... you're going to make me...
Of course we got to be here to specially event. Happy birthday, girl. I love y'all.
It's my birthday. Thank you so much, everyone! I'll see you guys soon, then. Okay?
Okay, goodbye! Goodbye, my friends. Thank you. Bye, everyone. See you.
There they go. Well, I guess that that means it's time for the singing portion. I did get to shake off some of the nerves thanks to my friends, because my heart's been racing today, but because I got to talk to them and I know that they're supporting me...
I feel good. I feel like we can put on a show
and I'll do my best. It's my first time really doing this, like,
live. So I'm trying not to run out of energy.
I got to take Kiara's idol expertise to heart.
I should know that too, being a rapper as well, but you know, I I forget.
I should know that too, being a rapper as well, but you know, I forget.
And plus, you know, the the speakers go boom, boom, boom all the time.
And plus, you know, the speakers go boom, boom, boom all the time.
Anyway, let's let's do a show, all right? Let's do a show, you guys.
Anyway, let's do a show, all right? Let's do a show, you guys.
I'll do my I'll do my best, okay?
I'll do my best, okay?
Nervous or tired? A little bit of both, but also ready to go.
Let's do this, okay?
Let's go to the stage.
imagine. Take a look, it's a changing age
and we're an open book that's got a lot to say.
Like a spiral, other's say "outta control",
but we just keep spinnin' still full that soul,
but we just keep spinnin' still full of that soul,
stayin' committed . to the sick vibes , good music
stayin' committed to the sick vibes, good music,
rhythmic rip - tide cruising , it 's proof , isn't it ?
rhythmic riptide cruising, it's proof, isn't it?
But you'll lose it, stuck on yesterday
cuz it only really matters if you play it that way.
'cause it only really matters if you play it that way.
How would you rate this ? add it to your playlist ?
How would you rate this? Add it to your playlist?
got something to say ? but only when your faceless ?
Got something to say, but only when you're faceless?
face this :
Face this:
you ain’t gotta be held back
You ain't gotta be held back by the status quo,
by the status quo , when the odds are stacked , we ' ll make a badass show ,
when the odds are stacked, we'll make a badass show.
誰にだってawayなご時世
In times when you're treated like an outsider,
新しいことに挑むには
to take on new things,
いっそ開き直り切るぐらいの方がちょうどいい
it's better to just completely shrug it off.
可笑しくない don't be surrender 3 秒 で わから せ て
It's not funny, don't be surrender, make you get it in 3 seconds.
ヤマ ナイ it 's awesome 拍手 喝采 進化 する flow
Yama-nai, it's awesome! Applause, cheers, evolving flow.
次元 を 超え て reaching anyone その ココロ を 射貫い て
Reaching anyone across dimensions, piercing through your heart,
重 鳴り響い ていく spiral tones
these are the spiral tones resounding deeply.
ここらで勝手な想像 考察 厨もそろそろ湧いてそう
By now, self-absorbed theorists and critics are crawling out,
揚げ足 とり 野暮 苗 な 呟き 誰得 で 寒い 不毛 な 論争
nitpicking and mumbling—a pointless, cold, sterile debate.
簡単に考えりゃいいよ 厄介な心配は無用
Just keep it simple, troublesome worries are unneeded,
ありもしない 境界線 なんて nonsense
imaginary boundaries are just nonsense.
これで開眼 出来たら 箇条 書き 最大限 hi-fi で 体 を 震わす 音 の 発信 なら どうだい
If this opens your eyes, listing it out with maximum hi-fi—how's this music that shakes your body?
それでも ムカッカン ない なら は い 来世 へ どうぞ ハイライ セイエドウゾ
If you still aren't feeling it, then right this way to the next life!
All of y’all ’s ideologies hella ancient
All of y'all's ideologies hella ancient,
jump , fall , no apologies , but your anxious
jump, fall, no apologies, but your anxious
creation is thankless , demolition ’s imminent
creation is thankless, demolition's imminent,
wait in ’ for the movement ? nah , just beginning it
waitin' for the movement? Nah, just beginning it.
first try , winging it , do you have an issue ?
First try, winging it, do you have an issue?
limitless , bringing this , sick of biased reviews
Limitless, bringing this, sick of biased reviews.
嫌 だ ? ya don ’ t say , but hey guess what ?
Apa? Ya don't say, but hey guess what?
you ’re old news . done living with your eyes wide shut ?
You're old news, done living with your eyes wide shut?
嵌れ て ない don ' t be so nervous 3 分 で 口ずさめる
Not getting hooked? Don't be so nervous, hummable in 3 minutes.
ツヅケテ it 's awesome 震天動地 増え て いく flock
Keep going, it's awesome! Earth-shaking, growing flock.
次元 を 超え て reaching anyone その 期待 値 追い抜い て
Reaching anyone across dimensions, surpassing all expectations,
御座 なり なんて ない spiral tones
never perfunctory spiral tones.
can ’ t ignore forever what could make you better
Can't ignore forever, what can make you better?
anyway , anyway , anyway , no wonder !
Anyway, anyway, anyway, no wonder!
嫌い が 好き に 変わっ たって 可笑しくない don ' t be surrender 3 秒 で わから せ て
Even if hate turned to love, it's not funny, don't be surrender, make you get it in 3 seconds.
ヤマナイ it 's awesome 拍手 喝采 進化 する flow
Yama-nai, it's awesome! Applause, cheers, evolving flow.
次元 を 超え て reaching anyone その ココロ を 射貫い て
Reaching anyone across dimensions, piercing through your heart,
重 鳴り響い ていく spiral tones
these are the spiral tones resounding deeply.
ここらで勝手な想像 考察 厨もそろそろ湧いてそう
By now, self-absorbed theorists and critics are crawling out,
揚げ足 とり 野暮 苗 な 呟き 誰得 で 寒い 不毛 な 論争
nitpicking and mumbling—a pointless, cold, sterile debate.
簡単に考えりゃいいよ 厄介な心配は無用 ありもしない 境界線 なんて nonsense
Just keep it simple, troublesome worries are unneeded, imaginary boundaries are nonsense.
これで開眼 出来たら 箇条 書き 最大限 hi-fi で 体 を 震わす 音 の 発信 なら どうだい
If this opens your eyes, listing it out with maximum hi-fi—how's this music that shakes your body?
それでも ムカッカン ない なら は い 来世 へ どうぞ ハイライ セイエドウゾ
If you still aren't feeling it, then right this way to the next life!
嫌い が 好き に 変わっ たって 可笑しくない don ' t be surrender 3 秒 で わから せ て ヤマナイ it 's awesome
Even if hate turned to love, don't be surrender, make you get it in 3 seconds, yama-nai, it's awesome!
拍手 喝采 進化する flow 次元を超えて reaching anyone そのココロを射貫いて 重鳴り響いていく spiral tones
Reaching anyone across dimensions, piercing your heart, these are the spiral tones resounding deeply.
Thank you ! Thank you everyone !
Thank you! Thank you everyone!
Thank you so much !
Thank you so much!
最高で ! ありがとう ございます ! 最高 ね 、 すごい 楽しかっ た リカ さん 本当に ! ありがとう 、 聞い て くれ て ありがとう !
That was the best. Thank you so much! It was so much fun, Rikka-san, truly! Thank you, thank you for listening!
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Thank you so much! Rikka-senpai, I'm so happy.
ついに一緒にやれたね、なんか
We finally got to do this together, somehow.
Finally!
ねぇ、ようやくね
Yeah, finally.
Yeah, we can perform on the same stage together.
なんか、前ね、約束、プロミス、してたんだよね
Remember we promised before?
You're right! We promised before you invite um your special day.
You're right! We promised before, for, um, your special day.
Of course, of course, thank you for coming here on my special day.
And I loved making Spiral Tones together with you. すごい、えっと、なんか、Spiral Tones作るのがすごい楽しかった
And I loved making Spiral Tones together with you. It was so much fun.
楽しかった
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah, right? いつかさ
Yeah, right? Someday...
また、すごい素敵な曲作りたいと思います
I'd love to make another amazing song together sometime.
ああ、もう！また作ろう！全部英語のとかね
Oh, let's make another one! An all-English one, or something.
ああ、そうね！An all English song?
Oh, right! An all-English song?
An all English song, I wonder, できるかな？
An all-English song, I wonder... can I do it?
絶対できると思う！頑張ったら絶対できるよ
I'm sure you can do it! If you try your best, you definitely can.
リカ先輩の英語、あの、なんか少しずつ、あの、なくなってきてきた、と思う
Rikka-senpai, your English has been getting a little bit... less, I think.
本当に？ Thank you と思います
Really? Thank you, I think.
すごい！頑張る頑張る
Amazing! I'll do my best.
頑張ってね！また曲ね、一緒に作ったり、Please, of course. とライブも
Do your best! And let's make another song together, please, of course, and do lives too.
Yes. 全体で頑張りましょう、ライブね。Yes, let's do it! Yeah, thank you.
Yes. Let's all work hard for the live, right? Yes, let's do it! Yeah, thank you.
And I always support Holostars. ホロスターズ、いつも応援しています。本当にありがとうございます
And I always support Holostars. I'm always cheering for Holostars. Thank you so much.
本当に頑張ってくださいね。ホロスターズもめちゃ素敵だともう
Please keep doing your best. I think Holostars is really wonderful too.
Here I have Ian. やさしい。やさしい。Thank you, my friend. エリカ、thank you so much.
Here I have Ian. So kind, so kind. Thank you, my friend. Rikka, thank you so much.
Great singer. Great singer too, and guitar!
すごい！ギター、ぜんぜんでき、できない、私
Amazing! Guitar, I can't do it at all, me.
できないくみ？ むずかしい。うざいよ
You can't? It's difficult. It's noisy.
Rap, rapができればね。Thank you. We have our specialties, 得意、得意なとこ
If you can rap, right? Thank you. We have our specialties, things we're good at.
まあ、一緒にね、いろいろ、そうね、やれば、全部いい感じになるよ
Well, if we do various things together, right, everything will turn out great.
Right, combine our power, nice combination! Nice combination!
それが一番だと思う。ありがと。うん、ありがとうございます、リカ先輩
I think that's the best. Thank you. Yeah, thank you so much, Rikka-senpai.
またね。ありがとね。また絶対やりましょう。See you next time. Goodbye, senpai, bye bye, リダ！
See you again. Thank you. Let's definitely do it again. See you next time. Goodbye, senpai, bye bye, Rikka!
See you! Goodbye, senpai! Bye bye!
Gosh, Rikka-senpai's so cool. Man, what a what a awesome dude and great musician.
Gosh, Rikka-senpai's so cool. Man, what an awesome dude and great musician.
Check out Rikka's stuff, please. Um, check out Rikka's channel. He does a lot of music stuff. I know that a lot of my Deadbeats love my music and stuff like that that I make.
So I always have my recommended musicians amongst the HoloCrew and Rikka's definitely one of them. And check out the stars 'cause they're working super hard too.
Now then, since we started off with a guest song, I figure it's probably time for me to to take it on my own. But I need a little bit of water. This always happens. At every show I go to, it's like every single song that I do, that I do, it's like in between I'm like, "Okay, water, water." It's become a joke, honestly.
Now then, since we started off with a guest song, I figure it's probably time for me to take it on my own. But I need a little bit of water. This always happens at every show I go to. It's like every single song that I do, in between I'm like, "Okay, water, water." It's become a joke, honestly.
Hold on.
All right. Oh, by the way, check out the stage. You see that cool skeleton?
Yeah, this is my special hololive made-to-order Calliope Mori stage, um, with my cool skeletons with the wings designed after uh the dear Mori album art by Ray.
Check it, check out my gaikotsu-tachi!
My skeletons, just like you guys sitting behind me, supporting me. Couldn't have skeleton backup dancers this time and next time, you'll be watching.
My skeletons, just like you guys sitting behind me, supporting me. Couldn't have skeleton backup dancers this time, but next time, you'll be watching.
Anyway, shall we go to the next song? Let's do it! The Grim Reaper is a Live-Streamer!
(3, 2, 1, swing it)
わたし 正体 不明 レディ
I'm a mysterious lady,
(deadbeats swinging now, outta control)
sha la la la la la
誰も 気づか ない
nobody notices,
(nobody notices, but hah, you know)
煌々
shining bright,
宵には
into the evening,
never missing moon
今 あなた の 隣 に 死神 が います よ
Right now, a reaper is right by your side.
let's hit the crosswalk, less talk / can you keep up?
you kinda 気になる、looking like i don't sleep enough
you kinda bug me, looking like I don't sleep enough
a 適当な rendezvous? we're bound to stray far
a casual rendezvous? we're bound to stray far
i'm the kind to ease your mind by taking you to the graveyard!
step out to the city, but 'cha don't know me
take my wits right with me, but they don't own me
maybe feel like going psycho in the streets / save it for later.
instead, i'll make a stylish retreat, and hit / go live, ro-high, so fly...
instead, i'll make a stylish retreat, and hit / go live, ro-high...
so fly, oh my, no drive, this guy, talk about a misfire
leave it to "miss fire spitting" for cash
i'll never be caught up again
writing this off as a passion, it's tough, i never had a life to begin with
and now i've got 2, double the power to sin with
but not like i'll complain / just laughing / just saying!
はらひら 感情 の 表裏 / 輝く 演奏 の 晴れ舞台
Fluttering emotions, front and back / The shining performer's brilliant stage
ってかさまさか 浮かぶ は 我が 調べ / 「 表 は どっち ？ 」 尋ね ない で ！
Or rather, floating up is my melody / Don't ask which side is the front!
dunno, dunno, dunno!
わたし 正体 不明 レディ / downtown 歌ってる
I'm a mysterious lady, singing downtown
sha la la la la la / 誰も 気づか ない
sha la la la la la / nobody notices
ヒールで闇を践破 / 煌々 宵には never missing moon
Crushing the darkness with heels / In the shining evening, never missing moon
(Three, two, one, swing it)
わたし正体不明レディ
I'm a mysterious lady,
dead beats, swinging now, outta control!
シャラララララ
sha la la la la la
誰も気付かない!
nobody notices!
(nobody notices but, haha… you know.)
爛々
Brilliant
宵には
in the evening,
「never missing moon」
"never missing moon"
今 あなたの隣に死神がいますよ
Now the reaper is right by your side
haha… yeah, right.
let’s hit
let's hit
the crosswalk, less talk, can ya keep up?
you kinda 気になる、 lookin’ like I don’t sleep enough!
you kinda care, lookin' like I don't sleep enough!
a 適当な rendezvous? we’re bound to stray far
A casual rendezvous? We're bound to stray far,
I’m the kind to ease your mind by taking ya to the graveyard!
I'm the kind to ease your mind by taking ya to the graveyard!
step out to the city, but ’cha don’t know me
Step out to the city, but 'cha don't know me
take my wits right with me but they don’t own me
take my wits right with me but they don't own me.
maybe feel like going psycho in the streets
save it for later. instead, I’ll make a stylish retreat, and hit
save it for later. Instead, I'll make a stylish retreat, and hit
“go live,” ro-high, so fly, oh my, no drive, this guy, talk about a misfire!
"go live," ro-high, so fly, oh my, no drive, this guy, talk about a misfire!
leave it to “miss fire spitting” for cash
Leave it to "miss fire spitting" for cash,
I’ll never be caught up again
I'll never be caught up again,
writing this off as a passion. it’s tough.
writing this off as a passion. It's tough.
I never had a life to begin with.
and now I’ve got 2, double the power to sin with.
and now I've got 2, double the power to sin with.
not like I’ll complain!
Not like I'll complain!
just laughing! no?
just saying!
はらり感情の裏表
Fluttering sides of emotion,
輝く演奏者の晴れ舞台
the shining performer's grand stage.
ってかたまさか浮かぶは我が調べ
Or rather, floating up unexpectedly is my melody.
「表はどっち？」尋ねないで！
"Which side is front?" Don't ask!
dunno! dunno! dunno!
わたし正体不明レディ
I'm a mysterious lady,
down town
downtown,
歌ってる
singing away.
シャラララララ
Sha la la la la la,
誰も気付かない
nobody notices.
ヒールで闇を践破
Crushing the darkness with heels,
爛々
brilliant
宵には
in the evening,
「never missing moon」
"never missing moon",
誰かを照らす
shining upon someone.
as far as tellin’ horror stories goes?
As far as tellin' horror stories goes?
my kinda warfare!
pull back the curtain
for one hell of a show
transmission live before you!
I’ll reap in real-time
I'll reap in real-time!
just don’t forget admission
Just don't forget admission,
that soul is still mine.
uh
out on the town again, death in your midst
right behind ya, down below ya, listen you get the gist, hah
nobody realizing, they don’t recognize me
Nobody realizing, they don't recognize me,
fine by me, it’s agonizing; “disguising”
fine by me, it's agonizing; "disguising".
live. now!! broadcasting
only so long-lasting
rather it’s a matter of a right and wrong casting
Rather it's a matter of a right and wrong casting.
fasten your seat-belts, faster breathing, need help!!
needing that fresh air. already seen hell.
「産まれた日に掛けられていた魔法が」
"The magic cast on the day I was born
解けていく日々の間で
in the days as it begins to wear off,
新しい魔法を上掛けしていくそれが人生」
casting new magic over it—that is life."
what do you mean?
どーゆー意味？って答えは自分で探してみて
"What's that mean?" Find the answer for yourself,
she said「月裏も表もない」
she said, "There's no back or front to the moon."
have a great night!
わたし正体不明レディ
I'm a mysterious lady,
down town
downtown,
歌ってる
singing away.
シャラララララ
Sha la la la la la,
誰も気付かない
nobody notices.
ヒールで闇を践破
Crushing the darkness with heels,
爛々
brilliant
宵には
in the evening,
「never missing moon」
"never missing moon",
誰かを照らす
shining upon someone.
as far as tellin’ horror stories goes?
As far as tellin' horror stories goes?
my kinda warfare!
pull back the curtain
for one hell of a show
transmission live before you!
I’ll reap in real-time
I'll reap in real-time!
just don’t forget admission
Just don't forget admission,
that soul is still mine.
sha la la la la la
hey listen.
今 あなたの隣に死神がいますよ...
Now the reaper is right by your side...
sha la la la la la
hey... hey! もしもし？
hey... hey! Hello?
ah, whatever
uh uh...
suisei! calliope!
呀呼 もう如何処しようもない呀
Hey, there's no helping it anymore!
アウトロー oh oh マリア
Outlaw, oh oh, Maria!
high & low 世界を獲りたいな
High & low, I want to conquer the world.
勝ち御堂 今宵 栄光のcrown
Seize the victory tonight, crown of glory!
yea あー ぶっちぎれ 内心本当は
Yeah, ah, burst through, deep down truly
説教とか勘弁でさ
spare me the lectures and preaching.
あー 失点だよ うっさいなぁ
Ah, it's a fault, how annoying!
「それって常識ですよ」とか
"That's just common sense," and all that
馬鹿馬鹿しい な
is so ridiculous.
前代未聞 な モン作ってんだってば
We're making something unprecedented,
bring you to heaven
road to be wicked
we just gotta break it
植え付けられている情報 (レーベル)
Implanted information (label),
疑え 今
question it now.
weh-oh-eh-oh
己の正当性と
Fighting against
戦うのか
your own righteousness?
we ain't gonna fake it
nobody can trick me
君と未来のため
For you and the future,
見つけていくんだよ
we will keep searching.
a shining shining star
届きそうだ
feels like it's within reach.
don't try to take it from... me
right now.
this a world where ya get what ' cha give
This is a world where ya get what 'cha give,
and i 'm a girl of a whole lotta adjectives
and I'm a girl of a whole lotta adjectives.
a couple might say “ stubborn , rude , hard to please ”
A couple might say "stubborn, rude, hard to please,"
and the crazys appraise me wit “ secret sleaze ”
and the crazys appraise me wit "secret sleaze."
now guys , please .
Now guys, please.
i gave first to get a lot
now i 'm spittin ' here with suisei , burning hot
now I'm spittin' here with Suisei, burning hot.
shining star
's bizarre
can't ya see the scars ?
can't ya see the scars?
we hit the grind , now we shine , look how goddamn far
We hit the grind, now we shine, look how goddamn far
we done came
a shame it 's a numbers game
A shame it's a numbers game
to some
fun first , fame second
Fun first, fame second,
we ain't dumb .
we ain't dumb.
because we livin ' in the moment and we own it , okay ? we done ?
Because we're livin' in the moment and we own it, okay? We done?
paving our way , for one
Paving our way, for one,
aim to outshine the sun
taming a loaded gun ?
Taming a loaded gun?
give it a try .
Give it a try.
ya better pick a direction and run .
Ya better pick a direction and run.
without an alibi
you can't deny
that maybe you been sleep in '
that maybe you been sleepin'.
come on get a grip , here 's a tip , don't stop dream in ' .
Come on get a grip, here's a tip, don't stop dreamin'.
road to be wicked
we just gotta break it
植え付けられている情報 (レーベル)
Implanted information (label),
疑え 今
question it now.
weh-oh-eh-oh
己の正当性と
Fighting against
戦うのか
your own righteousness?
とても不思議ね
It's so mysterious,
君といる時だけ
only when I'm with you,
胸を撫で下ろせるのか
can I set my heart at ease?
こうして can you stay with me babe
Like this, can you stay with me, babe?
他の誰も知らない 私見せたり
Showing sides of me no one else knows,
時間が止まればとか考えてたり
wondering if time would just stop.
恋焦がれた 夢の場所へ来たのよ long long way
We've come a long, long way to this longed-for dream place.
road to be wicked
we just gotta break it
上見れば 次のレベル
Looking up, the next level
近づいたら
gets closer.
weh-oh-eh-oh
己のモノサシで
By our own yardstick,
続けるの
we keep going.
知る度熟れて
Mellowing with every lesson,
優しさ覚え
learning kindness,
それぞれの幸せ
our respective happiness
皆わかっていくんだよ
we all come to understand.
just moving moving on
そんな運命だ
such is our destiny.
born to be wicked , and we aim to fly
Born to be wicked, and we aim to fly,
whether angels , or devils , it is do or die
whether angels, or devils, it is do or die.
no cap , kick it while the sound is hot
No cap, kick it while the sound is hot,
we broke backs just to get what we got
born to be wicked and we aim to fly
cuz we still ain't found that eternal sky
ya know ?
ya know?
そう生まれたんだ
That's how we were born.
i 'll find a way out
I'll find a way out,
we movin movin on ya
Yeah! Thank you!
Thank you! ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you! Thank you very much!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you, Calli!
Suisei-senpai! I got a hug! Suisei-senpai hug hug!
Yes, welcome to my stage! Yay!
どう思いますか？
What do you think?
あ、空気感がうまい。あ、酸いも甘い。
Ah, the atmosphere is great. Ah, sweet and sour.
嬉しい！なんかちょっと地獄のバイブス。ちょっと怖い気もすんだけどな。
I'm so happy! But it has a sort of hellish vibe. It feels a bit scary, though.
スリリング？
Thrilling?
スリリング！Yeah, Suisei-senpai likes the hellish vibes.
Thrilling! Yeah, Suisei-senpai likes the hellish vibes.
Thank you! ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
いや、カリオペとステージで歌えるなんて、あれ？あれ？
Man, to think I could sing on stage with Calli—wait? Wait?
久しぶりだね。久しぶりだね、カリオペ！Yeah!
It's been a while. It's been a while, Calli! Yeah!
Yeah, long time no sing together.
4日ぶりでしょ？Yeah, it's been like four days.
It's been like four days? Yeah, it's been like four days.
そうなんですよね！Right.
That's right! Right.
ねえ、で、私の周年ライブでね、アニバーサリーライブでカリオペを呼びまして、さっきの「Wicked」を歌いましたね？
You know, I invited Calli to my anniversary live, and we sang "Wicked" just now, right?
Yeah, Wicked is Suisei-senpai's song, and it came out with her new single, Template, and Template was number one on the charts and Wicked was number two, so omedetou, Suisei-senpai! ありがとー！
Yeah, "Wicked" is Suisei-senpai's song, and it came out with her new single "Template." "Template" was number one on the charts and "Wicked" was number two, so congratulations, Suisei-senpai! Thank you!
Amazing, so wonderful, and すごい楽しかったね！Wicked! すっごい楽しかった本当実に。
Amazing, so wonderful, and it was so much fun! "Wicked"! It was really, truly so much fun.
え、でも、今日はまだあるんだよね？
Uh, but today we still have more, right?
Yes, we have we have another song, actually, that we wrote together, except this time it's a it's a Calliope Mori featuring Hoshimachi Suisei song. Yes!
Yes, we have—we have another song, actually, that we wrote together, except this time it's a—it's a Calliope Mori featuring Hoshimachi Suisei song. Yes!
うん、A brand new song, and it's very important because after we perform this song, there's a really, really big announcement. It's the one. It's the announcement I mentioned, it's the biggest of my entire life.
Yeah, a brand new song, and it's very important because after we perform this song, there's a really, really big announcement. It's the one. It's the announcement I mentioned, it's the biggest of my entire life.
So please look forward to it, and it has something to do with the song we're doing. So we're going to do our brand new song. Yeah! It's called CapSule!
Yes! CapSule! CapSule with C-A-L-I-P-E-I, S-U for S-U-I-S-E-I-S-E-N-P-A-I. そうなんです-
Yes! "CapSule"! CapSule with C-A-L-I-P-E-I, S-U for S-U-I-S-E-I-S-E-N-P-A-I. That's right—
カプセルっていうふたりの新しい曲が出ますよ、皆さん！なんと二曲目！やったー！
A brand new song for the two of us called "CapSule" is out, everyone! It's our second song! Yay!
So please enjoy! Yes, let's check it out! Check it out!
And thank you so much Suisei-senpai for coming to my birthday! Yay! 楽しみましょう！じゃあね！Yes, join us! 頑張りましょう！頑張りましょう！
And thank you so much, Suisei-senpai, for coming to my birthday! Yay! Let's have fun! Bye! Yes, join us! Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
冗談めいちゃって あはは
Joking around, ahaha,
口論またやっちゃった
Arguing again, we did it.
酸いも甘いも苦いのもでも 飲み干せば alright
Sweet, sour, or bitter, if we drink it down, it's alright.
stand tough
not saints, nor sinners
man up
they say the winner takes all
ain't even sweatin' when the goin' gets rough and not leavin' til' that last light
間違いさがし嫉妬仕方ないなきっと
Spotting the differences, jealousy, can't be helped, surely.
ココロ七変化なんて本物の御本尊だ
Changing hearts like a shapeshifter, the real deity.
好き手前のお名前＝エンタメ、だめ？
The name right before love = entertainment, no good?
笑っちゃう でも溢れ出すのエモ
Laughable, but overflowing with emotion.
emotional wreck
but still i'm rockin' high spec
with every live it marks survival, where the mic check?
we boast an out-of-this-world devotion, stay neck-and-neck
cuz when ya chips are down, ya cards are out, the queens own this deck, haha
'cause when your chips are down, your cards are out, the queens own this deck, haha.
rhyme on my vibe
終わりはどうでもいいから期待させて
The ending doesn't matter, so make me expect more.
take you higher
聴かせてよ
let me hear it.
we start fires
火照るほどに
until we're glowing hot.
we're live wires
たまんないうまいbeat
an irresistible, great beat.
underrated, honest, encapsulate, astonish ya
read my lips 気付いてよ
Read my lips, notice it.
need a tip? わかるでしょ
Need a tip? You know it.
cuz we want it 解いてほしいの
'Cause we want it, we want you to solve it.
unfasten us and fascinate us
we can't wait faster, 'cause
したい (da la da, wo foo) ah yeah
want to do it (da la da, wo foo) ah yeah.
we want it all, and when i fall stay proud without any stall, my engine can't get louder
したい (da la da, wo foo) ooh
want to do it (da la da, wo foo) ooh.
we want it all, and when i fall i'm gon' rise i won't be your doll, but still i'm owning those eyes
ねえめんどくさいとか言ったらそれはいわゆる終わりじゃん
Hey, if you say it's troublesome, that's basically the end, right?
Why should I be tryin' for a dream that's a pain? 'Cuz death is dying every day designing rhymes for our gain, ya know?
Why should I be tryin' for a dream that's a pain? 'Cause death is dying every day designing rhymes for our gain, ya know?
ゼロからegoまで count up仕上がってどうぞあたしの子守唄
Count up from zero to ego, all finished, go ahead, my lullaby.
mellow doesn't suit our vibe, steady flowin' stellar, still, still it's a thriller, keep ya eyes on your mori, fellas
なんちゃって反省してるなんて嘘で引いて同情gotcha回してみて機嫌ガチャ当たるまで後悔
Just kidding, saying I'm reflecting is a lie, pulled you in with sympathy, gotcha. Spin it and see, mood gacha, regret until you win.
what's that? stop feeling sorry, just an act. i still don't care!
could maybe lay it down a million times i'll get fine when i can get my share
save it for the night
足りない同士で「どうして」を灰にして
With those who are lacking, turning "why" into ashes,
let's go
death star shoot across the sky, we the bad guys
お待たせしました (haha) shooting star あたし cutie star カワイイ もっとちょうだい
Thanks for waiting (haha) shooting star, my cutie star, kawaii, give me more!
tarinai, tarinai, ain't enough it's alright, we still got a couple fights in us, you know?
take you higher 聴かせるわ
Take you higher, let you hear it.
we start fires 火照るまで
We start fires, until we glow.
we're live wires キマッちゃう beat
We're live wires, an ecstatic beat.
underrated, honest, encapsulate, astonish ya
read my lips 気付いてよ
Read my lips, notice it.
need a tip? おそいのよ
Need a tip? You're too slow.
'cause we want it 期待の向こうへ
'Cause we want it, beyond expectations.
unfasten us and fascinate us, we can't wait faster, 'cause
したい (da la da, wo foo) oh yeah
want to do it (da la da, wo foo) oh yeah.
we want it all, and when i fall stay proud without any stall, my engine can't get louder
したい (da la da, wo foo) ooh
want to do it (da la da, wo foo) ooh.
we want it all, and when i fall i'm gon' rise i won't be your doll, but still i'm owning those eyes
冗談めいちゃって あはは
Joking around, ahaha
口説きまたやりゃっちまった
Flirting and messing up again
酸いも甘いも苦いのも
The bitter and the sweet
飲み干せば alright
Drink it all down, alright
stand tough
not saints, nor sinners
man up
the say the winner takes all
They say the winner takes all
ain't even sweatin' when the goin' gets rough,
and not leavin' til' that last light
間違いさ嫉妬仕方ないなきっと
Mistakes and jealousy can't be helped
ココロ七変化なんて本物のおんぼろだ
A changing heart is just a real wreck
好き手前の名前＝エンタメ、だめ？
The name before liking = entertainment, no?
笑っちゃうのでも溢れ出すのはエモ
Even if you laugh, what overflows is emo
emotional wreck
but still i'm rockin' high spec
with every live it marks survival, where the mic check?
take you higher
聴かせてよ
Let me hear you
we start fires
火照るほど
Until we're flushed
we're live wires
たまらない beat
An irresistible beat
ごめん、失礼しますが、死んでください～
Excuse me, but could you please RIP?
殺す事が楽しい
Murder is so fun
Excuse me, but could you please RIP?
ごめん、失礼しますが、RIP～
Sorry, excuse me, but RIP~
BY THE RULES, HELL, I'D LOSE IT
always be a prisoner to my ambition
last petals on the winds of desperation
flying for all this world to see
えへへ、皆さん！
Ehehe, everyone!
You got the rest,
Mori's in the building,
so you know you're already dead!
Oh my gosh, you guys are so... you guys are so surprised
and excited! Thank you.
Thank you so much, everyone! Yes...
the truth is, um... I am now signed to Universal Music!
Um, and I am doing... it's my major debut. I'm... I'm lost for words.
Um, this is like something I dreamed for for such a long time.
Um, honestly, I dreamed of doing something like this, and um...
yeah, I'm not gonna... I won't get emotional right now.
Um, we got a couple things to talk about, so... but yes,
I am debuting from Universal Music, and I will also be doing a solo live show in July!
My first solo on a real stage, in front of a crowd, in front of all of you guys!
So, let the Dead Beats empire continue onward, and there's a new EP...
major debut new EP called Shinigami Note. Shinigami Note, Shinigami Note, um...
Thank you everyone, um, who's been supporting me, and um... and uh yeah,
I'm really excited to see where this journey takes us. But I promise you guys,
I'll still be me. I'll still be making the music I want to make.
It's just going to be on a larger scale... I'm shaking right now.
And I wouldn't be here if you guys didn't love what I do so much.
So first, we have, of course, "CapSule," first major single.
And guess what, it's featuring my beloved singing senpai Hoshimachi Suisei,
QR code right now to pre-order, it's going to be released on July 20th,
July 20th, and that will include capsule.
By the way, Capsule's art was illustrated by Nardack, so let's give a big ups to Nardack as well.
But if you guys want to pre-order, and I recommend you pre-order because you get some cool stuff,
you can scan the QR code right now.
次に行きます！
Next slide!
Because if you order the first press limited edition, you get the LP sized set which is a CD plus DVD plus extras.
It's LP sized, but it's not a record, it's just like the size of a record.
But it's got the CD in it, um, the Shinigami Note EP CD as well as 5 original, uh, LP sized cover jackets drawn by various artists.
You guys are gonna love these pieces, these art pieces are so cool.
And then I also will be doing an interview, 30 minutes, uh, on DVD, behind-the-scenes of the creation of the EP.
And then also you get a crest badge, honorary Dead Beats crest badge.
Um, so yeah, that's pretty neat, but just so you guys know, these are super limited.
Like we only have a certain amount of them, um, so if you want it, you may want to try and grab it
before it's gone, uh, because these are not infinite.
Um, and it's, and we are never making them again, so, uh,
you may want to grab these as soon as possible, um, if you're interested.
And then we've got the standard version, of course, including the same songs, and then we have bonus items
depending on each outlet that you use to buy the CD.
So you'll see those items pretty soon when the, when the EP comes out, it's available for pre-order everywhere.
So again, scan the QR code if you're interested! 次に行きます！
So again, scan the QR code if you're interested! Next slide!
Let's go to the next slide and finally, my first solo concert, July 21st, 2022 at Toyosu Pit.
That's the day after the EP drops.
Um, I want to see you guys there.
More information coming soon,
but save the date.
And don't worry you guys, if you're overseas and you can't get to Japan, no worries because it will be streamed live to you and you will be able to buy a ticket for it.
So please don't worry about that, fans all over the world, you guys will get a chance to see it.
That's all, yoroshiku onegaishimasu! That's all. So, um, I figured the next song that I would sing would be, um,
sort of a celebration of moving on to the next.
I wrote this song, um, to kind of come to terms with me moving on from Japan's underground rap scene
and embracing, uh, what I have found here in Holo.
And things won't change with me in terms of Holo. I'll still stream for you guys and
and collab with my friends and do music collabs with them too. But when it comes to my original music,
Universal is going to be, uh, kind of, uh, with me throughout the journey.
So don't worry, I'm not leaving or anything. I'm still here.
But things may become a little more focused on the music. Things might change a little bit.
But again, I don't want you to worry. I'm only excited about this. So let's rather try and, and celebrate together,
um, looking towards a positive future with the next song,
end of a life. Let's go.
We'd run right through those nights
I'll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
There was madness in the meaning
Never laugh less, we were screaming
At the top of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
I'll fly, no proof, those heights
I'll never find another chance to say, hey, thanks for saving my life
I was hopeless, it was stinging
Running roadless, we were singing
At the top of our lungs to the numbness, this city never died
What was the root of it all?
I couldn't say.
Used to jump and then fall, rugged and cliché.
Would shrug it off without complaint, not a sound, no use in trying to find friends
'Cause in the end nobody sticks around.
It's when you shoved yourself into a crowded place that you turned around and found yourself in love in outer space.
Cue the reckless nights, no strings, laughing at our own dreams, just what the hell was so funny?
Up the wrong tree, stumble, used to falling great heights, amidst a concrete jungle, singing 'cause it felt right.
We mixed the ennui and troubles, rhyming our discontent, and though it's history, I can't forget the time that we spent.
Convinced that this could mean another end exists between real and pretend, a twisted alter-fiction where I missed my chance, did not ascend, and disappearing into the mist of never happened is the me that I can never befriend.
I let it go, fade in, fade out.
This crazy dream without a direction
Floating aimlessly.
There's nothing left back there for me.
Breathe in, but it won't stop the rain from pouring.
Breathe in, but it won't stop
the rain from pouring right
through those nights
I'll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
There was madness in the meaning,
never laugh less,
We were screaming at the top of our lungs
to the numbness, this city never died
Was there ever a song inside?
Chasing fireflies between the soaring high-rises left a trail behind
Silent singer, overworked and underpaid,
thinks an office is a coffin until off is where you're laid
Yet a thought persists, an optimist:
you ought to be afraid, saw the nothing wrong in writing songs behind the lonely shade
Is the world a sadder place without the words that you conveyed?
When the ladder fell and shattered every bar that we had played,
does it matter in the end the sound diminished and decayed
and your friends grew tired of fantasy, you're wishing they had stayed,
you don't get to say I miss you,
you watched your heroes fade into the rear view mirror
of the villain you portrayed,
stop the pity party, listen, you don't get to be dismayed,
you don't get to be emotional, feel blessed you got it made,
these the best of years of life because you chose to make a trade,
recollect the days you hoped and you prayed for this, what is there to miss?
Fade in, fade out, this hazy dream,
without a direction, roaming aimlessly,
there's nothing left back there for me.
There's nothing left back there for me.
Pretend it's the end of a made-up story.
I'll fly, no proof,
those heights, I'll never find another chance to say:
Hey, thanks for saving my life,
I was hopeless, it was stinging, driving roadless,
we were singing at the top of our lungs
to the numbness, this city never died,
I'll say goodbye to the soul inside,
and yet somehow, there was romance in our self-hate,
we've got no chance in this light maze,
but let's hold hands through the night haze,
we'll run so fast till the school chime,
till the train runs,
we know it's time, we're the sane ones.
Waking up now to the real life,
let me daydream till the next night,
I'll keep waiting,
I'll keep waiting for you.
Waking up now to my real life,
let me daydream till the next flight,
drowning so long, I got older,
now the crowd's gone, is it over?
Is it over?
Thank you so much, everyone!
Thank you!
Oh my gosh, all the hearts and the claps in the chat!
I saw so many people being so supportive in the chat, and you guys are amazing!
And I love you guys so much! Thank you so much for being my fans!
Honestly, it means the world to me.
And, um, and I have some other things to show you as well.
Um, my birthday merch! Of course, I made goods for you guys!
I wanted to make some really cool merch for my birthday as well, for my amazing Deadbeats! So let's go ahead and show them!
Tsugi ni ikimasu ne. Kore wa nihongo no setsumei desu. Iroiro arimasu yo ne. Katte kudasai ne!
Moving on. Here is the Japanese explanation. There's a lot of stuff, so please buy some!
Yeah. So, uh, we have many, many things here. Iroiro aru yo.
Yeah. So, uh, we have many, many things here. There's lots of stuff.
This are the alter version of Calli
from the UnAlive MV.
And it is super amazing.
It's the same size as the Yamori one,
so it's super big.
And it's going to look beautiful on your wall.
So I hope you guys will get it.
I'm looking forward to getting a bunch of them
and just putting them all over my house.
Then we also have the UnAlive album vinyl.
Right now, it looks like it's just front and back,
but it's actually a six-panel vinyl album.
So you fold it out and you get to see all of Rei's beautiful artwork
in beautiful six-panel glory.
So it's in the same format as the Yamori album.
Everything can be bought individually this time.
And if you buy everything together, you get a special printed letter from me with some choice words from your boy and also a signature.
So yeah, here's the sweater.
Check it out. Front and back.
On the back, you got my little Calli Mori logo crest at the top.
I designed this skull myself.
Looking to the side over there.
It's got a really cool neck.
Let's go next.
And then we've got my wine glass.
This is really cool.
I love, I can't wait to drink wine out of this.
Got my signature on it and everything.
Beautiful golden gradation at the bottom.
It's really lovely.
Next, we've got the poster.
Check this art out. I die every time I look at it.
Rei's work is just like a beautiful, beautiful painting.
So I hope that you guys will enjoy having this on your wall.
And next,
is there a next?
We got the, yeah, the album, that's right.
We've got the vinyl and it includes every single track from the album. Check it.
Um, but like I said, it's a six six panel, so you'll open it up and there'll be, there'll be more than just a front and back.
And it's really cool. You guys are going to love it so much.
Um, so yeah, that's all in terms of merchandise. Please look forward to a special letter from me. Uh, it'll be a printed letter from your boy to the deadbeats who get the full set.
And so yeah, look forward to that, please.
tanoshimi ni shite kudasai ne.
Please look forward to it.
Um, and yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed my birthday party.
But I do have one more song, one more song to sing to you guys,
a song that's very close to my heart about the world that we live in.
Because from now on, I'm going to be trying my best with Universal and really, really Gambaru from here on out.
Um, there's a world I want to see.
And um, and it's really beautiful.
But things right now seem kind of dark and dreary, you know?
Uh, it really seems some days like just the worst days are every day, right?
So, um, I would like to continue forward, um, singing songs that have, um, some kind of meaning to me, um, whether they be, uh, about enjoying yourself and just having fun, wacky and wild fun party songs or songs about our world, um, this song happens to be one of those more emotional ones.
But let's keep moving forward, uh, towards the world that we want to see.
Let's go. Scuffed up age.
Lost in thoughts of frosted frame of mind,
honest to god, it's just not our time.
Promises flawed by cosmic design.
Kore kurai dō tte koto nai,
demo namida no ato wa kesenai.
Coming of age, the stage doesn't light up
just right away, they told us it might've.
Yume wa mō akirame masu.
This cynical mind says: Why'd you try?
Why not give up and play the bad guy?
Wakatteru sa.
Unmei ga namidate nagara anata no moto sūru no nara
kuzureochi sō na karada dakishimeru kara.
We choose to know the struggles of this scuffed up age we're giving in.
Kusatta kuzu no hibi dakedo
kono yoake could seem a lot like not your day.
Soredemo anata o suteteshimawanai de.
Can't find a reason to stay.
Some busted world led astray.
Once trusted, left to decay.
We choose to go on anyway.
Lost in thoughts of always changing pace, allies and friends hiding more than one face.
Not really surprising, why are you compromising?
The sun is rising, a new horizon.
ふざけまいちゃって あはは
Joking around, haha
口説またやっちゃった
We got into another argument
酸いも甘いも苦いのも
Whether sweet, sour, or bitter
飲み干せば alright
Drink it all down and it's alright
stand tough
not saints, nor sinners
man up
they say the winner takes all
ain't even sweatin' when the goin' gets rough,
and not leavin' til' that last light
間違いさが嫉妬仕方ないないきっと
Mistaking difference for jealousy, surely
ココロ七変化なんて本物のおんぼろだ
A heart of constant changes is a piece of junk
好き手前の名前＝エンタメ、だめ？
My name before likes equals entertainment, no?
笑っちゃうでこそ溢れ出すのだエモ
I'd laugh, but emotion overflows
emotional wreck
but still i'm rockin' high spec
with every live it marks survival, where the mic check?
we boast an out-of-this-world devotion, stay neck-and-neck
We boast an out-of-this-world devotion, neck-and-neck
cuz when ya chips are down, ya cards are out, the queens own this deck
Cuz when ya chips are down, ya cards are out, queens own this deck
rhyme on my vibe
終わりはどうでもいいから期待させて
I don't care how it ends, just make me look forward to it
take you higher
聴かせてよ
Let me hear it
we start fires
火照るまで
To the point of glowing warmth
we're live wires
たまんなai beat
An irresistible beat
underrated, honest
encapsulate, astonish ya
read my lips
気付いてよ
Notice it
need a tip?
わかるでしょ
You know it, right?
cuz we want it
解いてほしいのか
Want you to untie us
unfasten us and fascinate us
we can't wait faster, cuz
したい
Want to
we want it all, and when i fall stay proud
without any stall, my engine can't get louder
したい
Want to
we want it all, and when i fall i'm gon' rise
i won't be your doll, but still i'm owning those eyes
ねぇめんどくさいとか言ったらそれは所謂終わりじゃん
Hey, if you say things are a hassle, that's the end
why should i be tryin' for a dream that's a pain?
cuz death is dying every day designing rhymes for our gain, ya know?
zeroからegoまでcount up仕上がってどうぞあずさの子守唄
Count up from zero to ego, finish it up and enjoy my lullaby
"mellow" doesn't suit our vibe, steady flowin' stellar,
"still, still it's a thriller, keep ya eyes on your mori, fellas"
なんて嘘で
Just kidding, it was a lie
引いて同情 gotcha
Pulling on your sympathy, gotcha
回して見て機嫌ガチャ
Spin it around, the mood gacha
当たるまで後悔
Regrets until you hit the prize
what's that? stop feeling sorry.
just an act. i still don't care!
...could maybe lay it down a million times, i'll get "fine" when i can get my share.
save it for the night
足りない同士で「どうして」を灰にして
With those who are lacking, turn "why" into ashes
death star shoot across the sky
we the bad guys
haha
お待たせしました shooting star
Thanks for waiting, shooting star
あたし cutie star “カワイイ” もっとちょうだい
I'm your cutie star, give me more "kawaii"
tarinai, tarinai, ain't enough
it's alright, we still got a couple fights in us, ya know?
take you higher
聴かせばよ
I'll let you hear it
we start fires
火照るまで
Until there's a glowing warmth
we're live wires
キメっ ちゃう beat
An intoxicating beat
underrated, honest
encapsulate, astonish ya
read my lips
気付いてよ even if
Even if you notice now
need a tip?
おそい のよ
It's too late
cuz we want it
期待の向こうへ
Beyond the expectations
unfasten us and fascinate us, we can't wait faster, cuz
したい
Want to
we want it all, and when i fall stay proud
without any stall, my engine can't get louder
したい
Want to
we want it all, and when i fall i'm gon' rise
i won't be your doll, but still i'm owning those eyes
capSule / Mori Calliope × 星街すいせい / 「capSule」 streaming now!
capSule / Mori Calliope × Hoshimachi Suisei / capSule streaming now!
Mori Calliope / Major 1st EP / SHINIGAMI NOTE / 07.20 release from UNIVERSAL MUSIC
07.21.2022 at Toyosu PIT Solo concert Coming soon...
Mori Calliope 1st Solo Concert / July 21st 2022 Toyosu Pit / More info coming soon!
Why are you still here?
Go check out the capsule MV!
It's happening in five minutes!
Five minutes on my channel, go!
Go, go, now!
Go watch the MV! Go watch the capsule MV!
Goodness gracious, bye!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Why are you still here? Go!
3D BIRTHDAY CONCERT ... WITH HUGE NEWS